wpcuonline.net 2013-05-03

# FACTS

                                                                                                              Rev. 07/2011
FACTS                 WHAT DOES MYCUMORTGAGE, LLC DO WITH YOUR
                      PERSONAL INFORMATION?
Why?                 Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives
                     consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you
                     how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to
                     understand what we do.
What?                The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you
                     have with us. This information can include:
                          Social security number and income
                          Account balances and payment history
                          Credit history and credit scores
How?                 All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday
                     business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’
                     personal information; the reasons myCUmortgage, LLC chooses to share; and whether you can
                     limit this sharing.
                                                               Does myCUmortgage,
Reasons we can share your personal information                                              Can you limit this sharing?
                                                               LLC Share?
For our everyday business purposes—
such as to process your transactions, maintain
your account(s), respond to court orders and legal                       Yes                             No
investigations, or report to credit bureaus
For our marketing purposes—
to offer our products and services to you                                No                             N/A
For joint marketing with other financial companies                       No                             N/A
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
information about your transactions and experiences                      Yes                             No
For our affiliates’ everyday business purposes—
information about your creditworthiness                                  Yes                            Yes
For our affiliates to market to you                                      No                             N/A
For nonaffiliates to market to you                                       No                             N/A
To limit              Call our Member Help Center at (800) 762-0047, ext. 7680 or (937) 912-7680
our sharing           Please note:
                      If you are a new customer, we can begin sharing your information 30 days from the date we sent
                      this notice. When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as
                      described in this notice.
                      However, you can contact us during business hours to limit our sharing.
Questions?            Call (800) 762-0047, ext. 7680 or (937) 912-7680 or go to www.mycumortgage.com

Page 2
Who we are
Who is providing this notice?      myCUmortgage, LLC (myCUm)
What we do
How does myCUmortgage, LLC         To protect your personal information from unauthorized access
(myCUm) protect my personal        and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.
information?                       These measures include computer safeguards and secured files
                                   and buildings. myCUm restricts access to non-public personal
                                   information about you to employees who have a specific
                                   business purpose for using it. Our employees are trained on the
                                   importance of customer privacy.
How does myCUmortgage, LLC collect We collect your personal information, for example, when you
my personal information?
                                   open     an account or apply for a loan
                                   show     your government-issued ID
                                   give us your income information or provide employer information
                                   We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit
                                   bureaus, affiliates, or other companies.
Why can’t I limit all sharing?     Federal law gives you the right to limit only
                                      sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information
                                       about your creditworthiness
                                      affiliates from using your information to market to you
                                      sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
What happens when I limit sharing  Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.
for an account I hold jointly with
someone else?
Definitions
Affiliates                         Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                   financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                   Our    affiliates include financial companies such as Wright-Patt Credit
                                      Union, Inc. (“WPCU”) and other affiliates of WPCU; affiliates of
                                      myCUmortgage, LLC include CU Realty of Ohio, LLC.
Nonaffiliates                      Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be
                                   financial and nonfinancial companies.
                                   Nonaffiliates     we share with can include companies such as credit
                                      bureaus, data processors, loan servicers, and mailing and distribution
                                      service companies.
Joint marketing                    A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that
                                   together market financial products or services to you.
                                   Our    joint marketing partners can include companies that provide
                                      mortgage or insurance products.
